OP
Hello, I'm Ui Hirasawa.
こんにちは 平沢憂です
My high school entrance exams are over.
高校受験も終わり
And this spring, I'll be joining my sister Yui at--
春 私はお姉ちゃんの学校に…
Ui!
憂！
W-Was your name there?
What's the matter with you, Sis? Why are you so nervous?
何で お姉ちゃんがそんなに緊張してるの？
Because...
だって…
My name was there. I passed, Sis.
あったよ 合格
Really?
ホント？
Uh-huh.
うん
お… お姉ちゃん 苦しい
Sis? I really can't breathe...
You did so good! You did great!
よくやった よくやったよ
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you so much! Thank you!
ありがとうございます
いや～ ありがとうございます ありがとう
It was thanks to the kind support of each of everyone of you here today
えっとね 憂が合格できたのも
that Ui managed to pass and begin her duty to her happiest successful life!
何を隠そう ここにいる皆様のおかげ…
Well, it looks like Ui passed.
合格みたいね
Looks like Yui is the happier of the two.
唯のほうが うれしそうだな
A doting parent?
親バカ？ いや 姉バカか
Or a doting sister's more like it.
It sure is shaping up to be a happy spring.
なんか ホンワリ幸せな春です
Congratulations, Ui!
おめでとう 憂ちゃん
Yeah, way to go!
やったな
Thank you, thank you everybody.
皆さん ありがとうございます
There it is.
あった
CHATTING NOW
Chatting Now
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
No no!
精一杯Study After School
study
hard
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
we can fly
Further than yesterday,
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
Jumping
now
Jumping Now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never Ending
Girls' Life
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Even if we
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
No no!
Shouting with all
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
歌えばShining After School
We'll
sing
for
you
After school
We're in the same class again!
また一緒ね
Mr. Akai's our homeroom teacher?
赤井先生が担任か
I wonder if I'll be in the same class as Yoshiko-chan?
よし子ちゃんと同じクラスになれるかな
And... there I am!
ええと…
あった ２年２組か
Second year, Class 2, huh?
Yeah, so am I.
私もだ
Oh, look, so am I, Class 2!
ホント？ 私も２組
Really? No way! That's great! How about you, Mio?
えッ！ じゃあ もしかして澪ちゃんも？
Class 1...
…１組
Hey, what's with those looks?
なッ 何 その目は
If you ever get lonely, come over to visit whenever you want!
寂しくなったら いつでも遊びに来ていいんだよ
What am I, a grade schooler?
私は小学生か…
フン 律こそ私と離れて大丈夫か？
Are you gonna be okay away from ME, huh?
You won't be able to crib off my homework!
もう宿題 見せてやれないぞ
へへ～ん 平気だよ
You don't have to worry about me! I'll have Mugi with me to help me out.
こっちには ムギがいるもんね～
ぐ…
Hello, everyone. A very good morning.
あッ 皆さん おはようございます
The uniform looks great on you!
似合ってる 似合ってる
You look so innocent!
初々しいわね
Y-You really think so?
そ そうかな…
Sis, your collar!
お姉ちゃん 襟
えッ？
You left the tag from the dry-cleaner on.
クリーニングのタグ つきっぱなし
Oh. Wow, you're right!
ああ ホントだ
And also, you've got a bad case of bed head.
それに ここんとこ 寝グセってるよ
I didn't have time to brush it this morning.
時間がなかったんだよ
Let's try to get up a little earlier starting tomorrow, all right?
明日からもうちょっと早く起きようね
Uh-huh...
うん
You know, maybe you two would be much better off if you switched ages with each other.
お前ら
姉と妹 交代したほうが いいんじゃないか？
Well, I'll see you later.
じゃあ また
I guess we should take off, too.
私らも行くか
Huh? Class-2 is up on the second floor?
あれ ２組って２階だっけ？
That's right.
ええ
It's like we're literally upperclassmen, now.
いかにも上級生って感じだよな
See you around, you Year 2, Floor 1, Class 1 student, you.
じゃあな １階２年１組の秋山さん
Oh yah, bite me!
…うるさい
We'll see you at break!
休み時間に また
Where on the second floor is it?
２階の どの辺かな
I think it's somewhere around...
I'm lonely...
…寂しい
また一緒だね
そうだね
一緒だな
There isn't a single girl here that I know...
誰も 知っている子がいない…
Mio! Glad to see you!
澪 よかった
I was worried I wouldn't know anyone when I was put in a different class than Yui.
唯とクラス離れちゃって
知っている人がいるか 心配だったの
Here's hoping for a good year together.
これから１年間 よろし…
Same here!
よろしく！
Freshmen!
Wanna join the Basketball Club?
バスケしませんか～
And the Tea Ceremony Club really is a lot of fun!
茶道部 楽しいですよ～
Consider the Occult studies Club.
オカルト研よろしく～
Are you interested in ping pong?
卓球に興味ありますか～
Wow, look at this, the halls are packed already!
わあ～ もう人でいっぱいだ
Large clubs certainly have more recruiting options.
やっぱり大きい部は手際が違うわね
Don't ever underestimate the Light Music Club!
軽音部だからって甘くみんなよ～
Mio, got the flyers?
澪 チラシは？
Flyer: Want to join a band?
Well, I kinda threw this together.
一応 作ってきたけど
うん… なんか普通
Kinda is right.
ガーン
It lacks any selling points.
ズバリ 売りがない
What exactly are our selling points.
でも 軽音部の売りって？
Something like...
そうだな 例えば お茶とお菓子はおかわり自由
"Come and join the Light Music Club, where you'll get all the tea and snack you want and get to sleep!"
食っちゃ寝 食っちゃ寝の軽音部
That sounds great!
あッ それいいかも
No it doesn't!
よくない
Well, do you have any better ideas? 'Cause the way it is now, it's got no impact!
じゃ～ ほかに何かあるか？
このままじゃ インパクトがないぞ
If it doesn't, we'll just give it some!
なければ つけるまでよ
We're the Light Music Club...
軽音部で～す…
We're holding a performance to welcome new students, meow.
明日 新歓ライブがありま～す
Please be sure to come, meow.
ぜひ来てくださいニャ～
If you are interested, come to the music room after school, woof woof woof!
興味のある人は
放課後 音楽準備室にどうぞ～ ワンワンワンワン
There's also lots of yummy snacks, cock-ah!
おいしいお菓子も いっぱいあるよ～ コケ～
Uh, Mio-chan...
ねえねえ 澪ちゃん
W-What is it?
な 何!?
It's doing the opposite of what we wanted.
これって 逆効果なんじゃ
Yeah, that just occurred to me, too.
私も今 思ってた
Oh, really?
へえ～ そうなんだ
Yeah.
そう
So, what club do you think I should join?
だから どの部がいいかな～って
It's a tough choice, huh?
迷っちゃうよね
うん
Ui!
憂～！
Big Sis?
お姉ちゃ…
Ui...
憂…
What was that?
あれ 何？
Beats me.
さあ…
We're the Light Music Club.
軽音部です
If you're interested, feel free to come by the Music Prep Room on the third floor after school.
興味があったら放課後 ３階の音楽準備室に ぜひ
Sure...
は はあ…
What the heck?
We get the music room all to ourselves!!
Want to join a band?
何 これ
You know you shouldn't run at people like that.
いきなり走ったらダメだろ
Yeah, I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
Oh, man, these things are way too hot...
ていうか これ暑すぎ
I think it's fun, like we're working at a part-time job.
そう？ バイトみたいで 楽しいけど
You sure do like working Mugi-chan.
ムギちゃん バイト好きだね～
Come on Azusa, let's go.
梓 行くよ
Uh-huh.
う うん
Sign: Preparation Room
After all that sweating, we hardly had any takers.
つらいばかりで あんまり受け取ってもらえなかったね
We'll just have to make up for it at tomorrow's performance!
明日のライブで 取り返すしかない
You're right!
そうね
Excuse me, but I made all these outfits for you, too!
あの～ この服も 作ってみたんだけど
Yeah, well, afternoon classes are starting.
さあ 午後の授業始まるぞ
The Light Music Club?
軽音部に？
Yeah, all the girls came across as being pretty cool. Wanna check them out?
うん なんか かっこいいイメージあるでしょ
行ってみない？
No thanks, so I'll pass. See ya.
あッ 私はいいや じゃあ
What's gotten into her? You'll come, right?
どうしたんだろ
憂は行くよね？
Sure, I guess. I'll go with you.
私はいいけど
Then let's go.
じゃあ 行こう
Azusa, Jazz Appreciation is having a welcome meeting in their club room up stairs.
梓 ジャズ研 ２階の部室で 説明会だって
Let's go!
早く行こう
あッ うん
Here it is.
あった
Excuse us. May we come in?
すみませ～ん
Welcome to our club room!
いらっしゃいませ
Uh... Big Sis?
お姉ちゃん
Oh, Ui!
あッ 憂ちゃん
You're joining the Light Music Club?
もしかして 軽音部に？
Wait! You two are dressed up, too?
律さんに 紬さんまで
Help me!
助けて～
Step aside, Please!
ちょっと どいてくれる？
Come in, come in. It's so good to see you, welcome to our club!
さあ 入って入って
歓迎するよ～
いッ いや あの…
First, could you explain what that was?
その前に 今のは
As I recall, it's supposed to be two doors down from the Occult Studies Club.
え～と 確か オカルト研の 隣の隣
イヤ～～～ッ！
I wonder what's up there?
この上って
I'm not exactly sure, but I think it's the Music Room.
確か 音楽室だったと思うけど
The Music Room, huh?
音楽室…
Ever since Christmas, it's like Miss Yamanaka has gotten totally addicted to putting us in different costumes.
クリスマス以来
さわちゃん先生 みんなに服着せるのクセになっちゃったみたいでさ
I see.
そうなんだ
Oh, I nearly forgot, this is Yui. She is my big sister.
あッ えっと
私のお姉ちゃんで唯です
I'm Yui Hirasawa.
平沢唯です ちょっと待っててね
If you wait just a minute, I'll go get you some nice tasty tea.
今 お茶持ってくるから
It's okay to take this one, isn't it?
これ持ってけばいいんだよね
It's pretty hot, so be careful, okay?
熱いから気をつけてね
熱ッ
Are you all right?
大丈夫？
S-Sis, are you okay?
おッ お姉ちゃん？
You just have a seat, Big Sis. I'll take it from here.
お姉ちゃんは座ってて あとは私がやるから
Are you sure?
そッ そう？
Oh, Yui...
唯…
Let me introduce Ritsu.
この人が 律さん
Hi there, I'm the club president, Ritsu Tainaka.
どうも～ 部長の田井中律です
Darn it, Ritsu!
ちょっと律
はあ？
She seems really cool.
かっこいい人だね
You still haven't submitted your request form to use the school auditorium!
講堂の使用申請書 まだ出してないでしょ？
If you don't, you won't be able to perform tomorrow.
明日 ライブできなくなっちゃうわよ
Oh, you're right...
そうだった…
I swear, how many times do I have to tell you.
まったく 何度言えばわかるの？
Sorry. I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい…
I want you to meet Tsumugi Kotobuki.
この人が 琴吹紬さん
It's a pleasure to meet you.
初めまして
And you, too.
どうもです
I'm so sorry for all the drama.
騒がしくて ごめんね
Wait, wait!
わッ まッ 待て待て
She seems like She's really nice.
優しそうな人だね
And what's with these silly getups, anyway?
大体 その格好は何よ
Hey, they weren't my idea!
私に言うな
Oh, my, Ritsu...
りっちゃんたら
And last but not least is, uh...
そして最後が… あれ？
Her?
あの人？
Yeah, her name is Mio Akiyama.
うん 秋山澪さん
It's just that she gets embarrassed really easily.
とっても恥ずかしがり屋さんなの
Huh? What's the deal, Mio?
なんだ澪
Quit hiding out there and come on in and join the rest of us.
そんな所にいないで 早く入ってこいよ
No way. You'll laugh at me.
イヤ 笑うもん
No, we won't laugh. It looks great on you.
笑いませんよ 似合ってますし
Y-You... You really mean it?
えッ ホント？
She's so cute!
かわいい～
Um... Ui, who's this lady?
あの… この人は？
This is Miss Yamanaka. She's their faculty advisor.
さわ子先生 軽音部の顧問
You two...
あなた達…
Yes?!
はい
Care to try on?
着てみな～い？
No thank you.
結構です
Please consider joining us.
じゃあ よろしくね
Thank you very much, we will.
ありがとうございました
So, what did you think?
どうだった？
うん…
It didn't quite seem the same as real jazz if you know what I mean.
本物のジャズっていうのとは 少し違ったかな
It didn't, huh?
そっかぁ～
Hey, why did you stop?
どうしたの？
That reminds me...
そういえば…
けいおん！
Wow, they look kinda cool!
わあ かっこいいかも！
Now they finally look like a Light Music Club.
やっと 軽音部っぽくなってきた
Mio-chan, my strap is caught on my shoulder.
澪ちゃん ストラップが肩に
Yeah, mine is, too.
うん 私も
I can't move in this skirt...
裾が邪魔
Yeah, these sleeves are... No, I guess they're fine.
袖が… あッ 大丈夫か
Dah! I can't play like this!
あッ もう やりづらい！
Whose bright idea was it to wear maid outfits?!
誰だ！ メイド服なんて言ったの
We decided to change into track suits.
結局 ジャージになりました
Okay, here I come!
お～い いくぞ
Ready!
あいよ～
Yeah!
You're next, Mugi! Go on!
次 ムギだぞ
Right!
はい
What do you think you're doing?!
何してんだ
Okay, why don't we get started, then.
じゃ～ 始めるぞ
うん
That was awesome!
わッ かっこいい！
They're cool, but not those track suits...
かっこいいけどジャージ
You really going? They were the ones in those animal costumes, remember?
ホントに行くの？
あの着ぐるみの人達でしょ？
I'm just gonna take a quick peek.
ちょっと のぞくだけ
Track suits?
ジャージ？
Hey, isn't that Ui Hirasawa? She's in our class.
あッ あれ 平沢さんじゃない？ 同じクラスの
It's almost like she doesn't wanna be there...
なんか困ってるっぽいね
Maybe they don't take things seriously in this club.
マジメにやってる部じゃないのかな
Um, we're really sorry we didn't give you a full-on proper performance.
なんか ちゃんと演奏見せてあげられなくて ごめんね
We normally go all-out when we play.
いつもはマジメにやってるから
Really? We do that?
そうかな～
Of course, we do!
そうだろ！
In any event, we'll be performing four songs tomorrow, so be sure to come.
とにかく 明日 ライブで４曲やるから 聞きに来て
We'll wanna hear your unvarnished opinion!
ぜひ 清き一票を
Sure, I'll do that...
はッ はあ…
Uh... Well, I guess we should get going then. I'll see you later on back at home, Big Sis.
じゃッ じゃあ そろそろ行こっか
お姉ちゃん 先に帰ってるね
Sure thing, Ui.
ほいほ～い
So, what did you think?
ど どうだった？
えッ？ ああ…うん いろいろすごかった
well, they're certainly incredible in many ways.
You think so?
そっか
Oh, and that cake we had was really good!
あッ ケーキはすごくおいしかった
Yeah, it was, wasn't it?
そ そうだね
Listen, I--
あッ あのね…
I'm sorry, I have to go to the bathroom! Go on without me. 'Bye.
ごッ ごめん ちょっとトイレ行ってくる
先行ってて じゃあ
Their prospects are looking grim...
こりゃ 望み薄かな
What did she think? What did she think?
どうだった？ どうだった？
She said, uh, she thought it was incredible.
うッ うん… すごかったって
Wasn't it, though? She'll come tomorrow, too, right?
でしょ～ 明日も来てくれるよね？
Yeah, probably...
うん… たぶん
The Light Music Club is really a blast!
楽しいよ～ 軽音部
Yeah.
うん
Hey, Big Sis?
お姉ちゃん
Yeah?
はあ？
What do you think is the best thing about the Light Music Club?
軽音部の一番いいところって どこ？
Huh? Well, let me think a second...
えッ？ う～ん そうだな
I guess it's how much fun it is.
楽しいところかな やっぱり
Fun in what way?
楽しいって？
I don't know. Fun is fun.
楽しいは楽しいだよ
Ah, do you wanna join, too, Ui? Our goal is to play the Budokan!
憂も入らない？
目指すは武道館！
I'll think about it.
考えとくね
Now that I do think about it, Sis has been really energetic ever since she joined the club.
確かに お姉ちゃん 軽音部に入ってから
生き生きしてるもんな
Until a little while ago, she...
ちょっと前までは…
Ui... Ice cream...
憂～ アイス
Not after you've had dinner!
ごはん食べてから
I want ice cream, ice cream!
アイス～
But now, she's really focused and working hard.
それが今は 一生懸命になってる
Ui?
憂
Yes, Sis?
何？
I really wanna have ice cream.
アイス食べたい
After you've had your dinner.
ごはん食べてから
In some ways she's the same as ever, though...
ちッ…ケチ
…変わってないところもあるけど
Sign: Freshman Reception
うわッ
It's packed out there!
人でいっぱい…
Well, it is supposed to be the welcome party for all the new students.
そりゃ 新入生歓迎会だからな
If we play like we always do, we'll be fine.
いつもどおりやれば いいだけ
B-But we don't...
で で で でも…
You're still not over your stage fright, huh?
結局 緊張するんだな
Ritchan! I just found a one dollar coin!
りっちゃん！
そこで100円拾った
I wish you would be more nervous.
…お前は もっと緊張しろ
The order is Fuwa Fuwa Time,
「ふわふわタイム」
Curry, Then Rice,
「カレーのちライス」
My Love Is A Stapler,
「私の恋はホッチキス」
Brush Pen, Ballpoint Pen.
「ふでペンボールペン」
Your taste in song titles is as unique as I've ever seen.
相変わらず 澪のセンスは独特だよな
Really?
そう？
So, do you really want me to sing all the vocals today?
ねえねえ ボーカル全部私でいいの？
That's right, we never decided on that.
そういや決めてなかったな
I've got it. Since we're lucky enough to have two singers, I think that you should do at least one song today, Mio.
そうだな せっかく２人いるんだし
澪も１曲ぐらい やったほうがいいんじゃないか？
C'mon, high five!
ほら ハイタッチ
No way! Forget it! I can't!
イヤだ 絶対イヤ
Oh, Mio...
澪ちゃん
But everybody loved you singing in our last show.
でも 前のライブで評判よかったし
Forget it!
ヤダ！
Come on, accidents like that don't happen twice.
あんなアクシデントはもう起こらないって
No!
ヤダ！
But, Mio...
でも…
Ugh!
ヤダ！
Mio-chan...
澪ちゃ…
No!
ヤダ！
You want ramen?
ラーメンだけじゃ
No!
ヤダ！
So then, no gyoza?
ギョウザもつかなきゃ
No!
ヤダ！
Boy, that's one serious rejection response.
すごい拒否反応だな おい
I guess we have no choice. We'll have to let Yui handle everything.
しょうがないわね
全部 唯ちゃんでいいんじゃない？
Next up is a club introduction and performance by the Light Music Club.
次は 軽音楽部による クラブ紹介と演奏です
あ 出番だ
Looks like we're on!
Break a leg. And I have just one last word for you all before I go.
頑張ってね
最後に みんなに一つだけ言っておくことがあるわ
What is it?
さわちゃん…
Uniforms as costumes are great!
制服も 意外といい！
Would you please clear off the stage now?
…早く舞台袖に下がってください
Really? You've decided?
えッ 決めちゃったの？
Yeah, the Jazz Appreciation Club has some cool upperclassmen in it.
うん ジャズ研究会にすごいかっこいい先輩がいて…
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
Well, if that's the club you wanna be in, then that's the club you should join. It's your decision after all.
そッ そっか
しょうがないよ
どこに入るかは自由なんだし
See you.
じゃあ
Uh, excuse me!
あッ あの…
Sorry to drag you with me like this.
ごめんね つきあわせちゃって
Oh, wow, it really is packed in here!
結構いっぱいだ
My sister is on vocals today!
お姉ちゃん ボーカルなんだ
Hi, we're the Light--
どうも… けッ…
The Light Music Club.
軽音部です
To all you new students out there, congratulations on getting into our school!
えと 新入生の皆さん
ご入学 おめでとうございます
When I first heard about the Light Music Club, I thought all they did was playing "lighthearted" music.
私 最初 軽音部って聞いて
軽～い音楽だと思ってたんですよ
Yui's banter is doing a good job putting everybody at ease.
唯のＭＣは 安心して聞いていられるな
I signed up without giving it much thought, thinking I could just play castanets or something simple like that.
それで カスタネットができればな～
なんて 軽い気持ちで入部しました
So I hope all of you think about joining up with the same carefree attitude!
なので皆さんも そんな感じで 気軽に入部してください
But you know, Miss Yamanaka told me one day that castanets are actually really hard to play.
あ でも
カスタネットは実は難しいって
さわちゃん先生が言ってました
Here's our next song.
では 次の曲
About time...
まったく
Oh, Miss Yamanaka is our advisor and the music teacher here.
あ さわちゃんって言うのは 音楽の先生のあだ名で…
What are we, a comedy band?!
コミックバンドか！
Sorry, Ritchan.
ごめん ごめん
Anyway, here's our next song, "My Love Is A Stapler"!
じゃあ次の曲
「私の恋はホッチキス」
That riff is tough, and she's pulling it off perfectly! Except for...
出だしのリフ難しいのに
完ぺきになってる… ていうか
Yui, sing!
唯 歌！
I forgot the lyrics!
歌詞忘れた…
I wonder why
なんでなんだろ
On this worrying night
気になる夜　キミへのこの思い
I'm writing my feelings for you on paper
便せんにね書いてみるよ
Mio-chan!
澪ちゃん？
Hurry up and sing!
早く歌え！
Perhaps...
もしかして
気まぐれかもしれない
I'm just being whimsical
But the number of sheets just keeps increasing
それなのに枚数だけ増えてゆくよ
It would be nice if I had an equation
好きの確率わり出す計算式
あればいいのに
For calculating the probability that I love you
キラキラひかる　願い事も
My sparkling and shining wishes
グチャグチャへたる　悩み事も
Have mixed in with all the things I worry about
That's right, I'll staple it
そーだ
ホッチキスで　とじちゃおー
Only at the beginning, my feelings were light
はじまりだけは　軽いノリで
Before I knew it, my passion grew
しらないうちに　あつくなって
もう針がなんだか通らない
And somehow staples can't go through it anymore
ララ★また明日
Lala See you tomorrow
Excuse me girls.
あの… 皆さん
You know, no one is going to come in with you glaring out the door like that.
そんな目で見てたら
来るものも来ないんじゃ
Aw, but the crowd at the show was so psyched about us!
だって せっかくライブ盛り上がったのに
Impossible not a single person showed up!
１人も来ないなんて あり得ない
あッ でも もしかして私が失敗したから？
You don't think it's because of the way I messed up, do you?
You know, maybe it's because we have such a low membership in our club.
やっぱり 部員が少ないのがいけないのかな
Come on now, the tea is ready.
お茶 入りましたよ
I suppose we're just gonna have to go and nab up Ui.
こうなったら 憂ちゃんを捕まえてくるしかないか
Here the poor girl isn't a bug.
虫じゃないんだぞ
Pardon me...
あの…
Uh, yes?
はい
I'm very interested in joining your club.
入部希望なんですけど…
えッ 今 何と？
Would you mind repeating that?
I'd like to join the club.
入部希望…
We got one!
確保～！
Good for you, Big Sis!
よかったね お姉ちゃん
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
I am
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
Um, what's this?
あの… これ 何ですか？
It's a pair of cat ears, obviously.
何って 猫耳だけど
No, I knew that. But...
いや それはわかるんですけど…
えっと これを どうすれば…
What am I supposed to do with them?
I wonder if they're testing me to see how independent I am.
もしかして 私の自主性が試されてるのかな…
Okay, it's your turn, next, Azusa-chan.
はい 次 梓ちゃんの番
Um, my name's Azusa Nakano, year 1, class 2.
えっと １年２組の中野梓といいます
I look forward to our time together.
これから よろしくお願いします！
New Club Member!